

Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

#### Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

#### Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

# Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

### E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

## Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

### Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

#### Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



Graduated in Management Processes, with an emphasis on Process Management and Optimization, and I have always had the desire to acquire more knowledge and evolve professionally, I got in touch with the technology area about 10 years ago and since the end of 2019, I have returned to the technology area. where I've been studying and taking different courses. In 2021 I started my MBA in Software Engineering, where I have learned many new things and evolved day by day.

I will continue to improve myself daily as a Front-end Developer and Software Engineer after graduation, seeking to acquire more experience and knowledge!



# **EXPERIENCE**

Full Technical Consultant 2022 - ....

VILT Brazil Information Systems
Fullstack Consulting, working with Java
in Backend and Angular/React in Frontend,
using Platform programs
Adobe Experience Manager(AEM),
providing services for
several clients such as Porto, CVC and etc.

E-commerce Analyst / Front-end Developer

2019 - 2021

DT3 Sports
Invoice issuance,
marketplaces,
content creation for campaigns,
website development in React.JS,
image optimization and
responsible for the integration of ERP Bling.

Office Assistant

2014 - 2018

Nova Lik Auto Peças Issuance of Sales Invoice Issuance of Payment Reports Input and Output of Products in Stock.

**Quality and Service Technician** 

2010 - 2013

Arcos Dourados LTDA. Coordinated employees in their respective functions, for better customer service delivery of a 100% qualitative product.



## ACADEMIC EDUCATION

Faculdade Única

2021 - 2022

Estácio de Sá - RJ 2018 - 2020 MBA Software Engineering

TECHNOLOGIST Management processes



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

### Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

#### Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

# Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

### E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

## Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

### Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

#### Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



HTML/CSS - 3 Years of Experience

Jquery/Javascript - 3 Years of Experience

Angular/React - 3 Years of Experience

VueJs/NodeJs - 3 Years of Experience

Git/Github - 3 Years of Experience

NPM/YARN - 3 Years of Experience

Wordpress/Shopify/Bling - 3 Years of Experience

Bootstrap/Typescript - 2 Years of Experience

UI/UX - 2 Years of Experience

Figma/Photoshop - 2 Years of Experience

Less/Sass - 1 Year of Experience

GitLab/Sketch - 3 Months of Experience

AWS/PHP - 1 month of Experience

Firebase/Laravel - 1 month of Experience

Markdown/Evernote - 1 month of Experience

Strapi/GraphQL - 1 month of Experience

MongoDB/MariaDB - 1 month of Experience

MySQL/NoSQL - 1 month of Experience

PostgreSQL/Express - 1 month of Experience

Babel/Webpack - 1 month of Experience

Postman/NextJS - 1 month of Experience

Jest/JUnit - 1 month of Experience

Mongoose/Nginx - 1 month of Experience

TailwindCSS - 1 month of Experience



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

#### Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

#### Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

# Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

#### E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

#### Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

### Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

#### Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



Bootcamp Eduzz - Fullstack Developer - Digital Innovation - 2022

Adobe Professional – Adobe Experience Manager Sites Business Practitioner - 2022

Adobe Professional – Adobe Experience Manager Front-End Developer - 2022

Working with Components in React - 2022

Component architecture and front-end complexity management - 2022

Let's Code Course (Santander) - Dev Fullstack - 2021

MERN Stack Course (MongoDB, Express, React & NodeJS - FaculdadeIV2 - 2021

Initial Vuejs Course - Vuejs Brazil - 2021

Basic to Advanced Javascript & Typescript Course (HTML/CSS/NodeJs/React/MySQL/PostgreSQL/MariaDB/ – Udemy – 2020

Digital Security Course - FGV - 2020

Business Financial Education Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Strategic Planning Course for Entrepreneurs - SEBRAE - 2020

Financial Management Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Customer Success Course (How to Conquer and Keep Customers)

– SEBRAE –
2020

Digital Marketing Course for Entrepreneurs - SEBRAE - 2020

Financial Strategy for Growth Course - SEBRAE - 2020

Basic Platform Security Course (CBSP) - Shelter Courses, 2018

Submerged Aircraft Escape Training (HUET) – Shelter Courses, 2018

Administrative Assistant Course - 24-hour Courses - 2016



Hudson Kennedy
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER
SOFTWARE ENGINEER
UI/UX DESIGNER

### Address:

Engoá street, 167 - Rio de Janeiro -Brazil

#### Phone:

(21) 9 6960-9121

# Portfolio:

https://hudsonkennedy.vercel.app

### E-mail:

hudsonhugo90@gmail.com

#### Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hudsonkennedyjr/

### Github:

https://github.com/Hudsonjr90

## Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/ \_hudson.9kj/



Spanish - Basic

French - Basic

Italian - Basic

English - Advanced



# **ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES**

Excel

Word

**Power Point** 

**Teams** 

Outlook

Sketch

Wordpress

Shopify

**ERP Bling** 

**System Configurations** 

Windows

**Computer Domain** 

**Typing** 

document archiving

internet in general

Google Chrome

Mozilla

Opera